[
  {
    "question": "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?",
    "correct_answer": 1,
    "answers": [
      "Humanity",
      "Health",
      "Honour",
      "Household"
    ],
    "prize": "$500"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
    "correct_answer": 2,
    "answers": [
      "Pocahontas",
      "Sleeping Beauty",
      "Cinderella",
      "Elsa"
    ],
    "prize": "$1,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "What name is given to the revolving belt machinery in an airport that delivers checked luggage from the plane to baggage reclaim?",
    "correct_answer": 0,
    "answers": [
      "Carousel",
      "Concourse",
      "Terminal",
      "Hangar"
    ],
    "prize": "$2,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these brands was chiefly associated with the manufacture of household locks?",
    "correct_answer": 1,
    "answers": [
      "Phillips",
      "Chubb",
      "Flymo",
      "Ronseal"
    ],
    "prize": "$4,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "The hammer and sickle is one of the most recognisable symbols of which political ideology?",
    "correct_answer": 3,
    "answers": [
      "Republicanism",
      "Conservatism",
      "Liberalism",
      "Communism"
    ],
    "prize": "$8,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which toys have been marketed with the phrase “robots in disguise”?",
    "correct_answer": 3,
    "answers": [
      "Hatchimals",
      "Sylvanian Families",
      "Bratz Dolls",
      "Transformers"
    ],
    "prize": "$16,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the word loquacious mean?",
    "correct_answer": 0,
    "answers": [
      "Chatty",
      "Angry",
      "Shy",
      "Beautiful"
    ],
    "prize": "$32,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Doctor Who, what was the signature look of the fourth Doctor, as portrayed by Tom Baker?",
    "correct_answer": 1,
    "answers": [
      "Pinstripe suit and trainers",
      "Wide-brimmed hat and extra long scarf",
      "Cape, velvet jacket and frilly shirt",
      "Bow-tie, braces and tweed jacket"
    ],
    "prize": "$64,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these religious observances lasts for the shortest period of time during the calendar year?",
    "correct_answer": 2,
    "answers": [
      "Lent",
      "Ramadan",
      "Diwali",
      "Hanukkah"
    ],
    "prize": "$125,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the closest point, which island group is only 50 miles south-east of the coast of Florida?",
    "correct_answer": 0,
    "answers": [
      "Bahamas",
      "US Virgin Islands",
      "Turks and Caicos Islands",
      "Bermuda"
    ],
    "prize": "$250,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "Construction of which of these famous landmarks was completed first?",
    "correct_answer": 2,
    "answers": [
      "Eiffel Tower",
      "Empire State Building",
      "Big Ben Clock Tower",
      "Royal Albert Hall"
    ],
    "prize": "$500,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina??",
    "correct_answer": 0,
    "answers": [
      "Blackbeard",
      "Calico Jack",
      "Bartholomew Roberts",
      "Captain Kidd"
    ],
    "prize": "$1,000,000"
  }
]